100pulse.com 2014-06-25

# 100pulse.com Website Monitoring Service Privacy Policy

Summary

100pulse values and respects the privacy of the Company's Subscribers to our free and fee-based services. Because we gather certain types of information about our Subscribers we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the 100pulse Web site that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated by 100pulse, its partners. These privacy practices apply only to online transactions, activity and to all email communications. All credit card transactions are processed through secure connections. 100pulse uses proven technologies that improve the privacy of our Subscribers' information. 100pulse will not sell your email address to anyone without your express permission and we control all e-mail delivery to assure your privacy. When we do share information with our partners and advertisers, it is in aggregate form, and does not identify you personally. 100pulse does not collect or use any information about you except for the information that you provide or is publicly available, and this information is used solely to make the services provided more relevant to your interests. Under no circumstances is your e-mail address ever shared with advertisers. 100pulse provides both free and fee-based services. The free services are supported by our advertisers and sponsors. By becoming an 100pulse Subscriber, you agree to the 100pulse Services Agreement Terms and Conditions. This includes your agreement to receive communications including monitoring alerts, weekly reports, announcements, updates and other carefully screened special offers and promotions. This is essential to maintaining certain services free to our subscribers. If you do not wish to view and receive such communications, you may cancel your account or contact us at [privacy@100pulse.com](mailto:privacy@100pulse.com)

1\. What Personally Identifiable Information Does 100pulse Collect? 

100pulse's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Because 100pulse derives its revenue mainly from advertising and fee-based services, collecting information is essential to keeping certain of our services free. It is also necessary to assure the relevancy of this advertising to our Subscribers. 100pulse collects personally identifiable information when a Subscriber provides it to us, such as when you subscribe to our services, update your Subscriber profile on our Web site, respond to our weekly email reports and monitoring alerts, and when you visit the 100pulse Web site. 100pulse may also receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you have provided to us. 

2\. What Anonymous Information Does 100pulse Collect? 

Cookies 

Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. However, cookies tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit the 100pulse site, although active participation in certain areas of our site may require cookies. In addition, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected by selecting certain options on your browser. 

Visitor Activities 

To track general Subscriber traffic patterns, we use electronic images known as single-pixel GIFs, transparent GIFs, or clear gifs. 100pulse also automatically receives and records information from our servers and from your browser including your IP address, the time, and information about the page you requested. In order to determine which features Subscribers find most useful, we use tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including: keeping count of return visits to our site or our advertisers' or partners' sites and accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on Web site and advertisement usage. 

Third-Party Advertisement Servers 

Some of our advertisers use third-party companies to serve their advertisements on our site and, in some cases, in our HTML-formatted email reports. Often, these third-party advertising companies employ cookie and visitor activity technologies to measure advertisement effectiveness. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Use of their tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies. If you would like more information about the privacy policies of the third-party advertising providers including information on how to opt out of their tracking methods, check their respective sites. 

3\. How Does 100pulse Use The Subscriber Information Gathered? 

100pulse uses the information we gather for the following purposes:   
(i). To notify you with our monitoring alerts and weekly reports related to the availability of your Web site.   
(ii). To enhance the Subscriber experience we use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate Subscriber demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.  
(iii) To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling Subscribers to participate in polls and contests.   
(iv) To customize the promotions, advertising and content you see, which helps keep certain of our services free to Subscribers. This allows our sponsors and advertisers to market their products and services more effectively, and allows our Subscribers to receive promotions and advertisements that are pertinent to their interests and needs. This, in turn, helps keep certain of our services free to Subscribers.   
(v) • To send Subscribers information about 100pulse as well as announcements, updates and other carefully screened special offers and promotions from 100pulse and our partners. Subscribers may expect to receive no more than four special offers or promotions by email per month. 

4\. How Does 100pulse Share The Information? 

Personally Identifiable Information 

The following paragraphs describe how the Company currently uses personally identifiable information, but the Company may change or broaden its use at any time as permitted by law. 100pulse will not sell your email address to anyone without your express permission and we control all email delivery to assure your privacy. 

Compliance with Laws and Communications with Legal Authorities 

100pulse responds to subpoenas, court orders and legal requests from authorities. We may contact the authorities if we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, 100pulse's Services Agreement Terms and Conditions, usage guidelines for specific products or services, threaten the rights, property or safety of 100pulse, our Subscribers, or others. 

Aggregate Information 

You agree to pay 10100pulse aggregates personally identifiable information and discloses such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional and other purposes. 

5\. What Are Your Options? 

Subscribers provide Subscriber data requested by our activation process. The 100pulse Services Agreement Terms and Conditions requires Subscribers to receive email communications including monitoring alerts, weekly reports, announcements, updates and other carefully screened special offers and promotions. This is essential to maintaining certain services free to our subscribers. If you do not wish to view and receive such communications, you may cancel your account or contact us at or contact us at [privacy@100pulse.com](mailto:privacy@100pulse.com)

6\. How Can You Update Your Personally Identifiable Information? 

Unless stated otherwise on 100pulse's web pages applicable toYou can correct or change the information collected during activation for any service can be done from accounts page. Subscribers may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. Subscribers who are experiencing problems or who have questions about how our services work can contact 100pulse using the email address [privacy@100pulse.com](mailto:privacy@100pulse.com). 

7\. How Will You Know If The Privacy Policy Is Changed? 

By visiting the 100pulse Web site, becoming a Subscriber, or using the free or fee-based services, you hereby provide your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and are aware that our policy may change over time. Specifically, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect new features, services and options, and any changes on the use of personal information. Continued use of the 100pulse Web site and its services will indicate that you agree with any changes. Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected within this area of our Web site. 

8\. Privacy of Children 

Our Web site is not directed to children. We do not knowingly permit registration by and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age. 

Questions, Comments 

Questions regarding this privacy statement, or any other aspects of our Web site or email communication, should be sent via email to our corporate offices at: [privacy@100pulse.com](mailto:privacy@100pulse.com)
